<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>d</title>
    <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on d</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ca</language>
    <atom:link href="bfirm.netlify.app/ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accountancy</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practiceacc/account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practiceacc/account/</guid>
      <description>Accountancy is one of the backbones of businesses and companies daily activity. Our firm takes full control and responsibility in this area and guarantees a strict fulfilling of the demanding compliance requisites.
Besides, we are aware of the burden for businesses to supply information on a daily basis, and we offer flexibility on that aspect, also taking into consideration the financial needs of the business or company.
Our experience in Accountancy Our firm specializes on businesses and small size companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Law</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicebus/bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicebus/bus/</guid>
      <description>The day-to-day of business activity it is not a clear path. From advisement to litigation our firm provides a steady and experienced counsel to help achieve the businesses and companies goals.
Every business is different and we have experience dealing with local and international businesses and their unique needs.
Our experience in Business Law Our experience covers a wide variety of matters in Business Law, including:
Loan transactions Bankruptcy Law Contracts Patents Trademarks Commercial Litigation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil Law</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicecivil/civil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicecivil/civil/</guid>
      <description>The situations of conflict that can occur on just normal individual activity are almost endless. Whether the dispute arise in a will, purchase or some injury suffered, a trusted advisement is essential for prevention or deciding the next step. Our firm will be attentive on the details of your case and will offer a full guidance throughout the conflict navigation.
In some cases, though it may take months or years, litigation is unavoidable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicecom/comp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicecom/comp/</guid>
      <description>Our firm offers a fully integrated monitorship for the major compliances duties for the businesses or companies, including taxes, working contracts and accountancy. This unitary approach allows an exhaustive dedication, besides a deeper knowledge on the inner workings of our clients, enhancing thus, the quality of our service.
Our experience in Companies Our experience with several businesses and companies shows us that with this approach our values and management principles of proximity and confidence are totally fulfilled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact us below to book an appointment Use the form below to tell us about your legal inquiry, and we’ll call you back to schedule an appointment. You may also email or call us to make an appointment. Our general response time is one business day.
We cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security or confidentiality of any communication made via e-mail. If you wish to provide information of a confidential or sensitive nature to us, please contact us directly by telephone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Law</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicescorp/corp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicescorp/corp/</guid>
      <description>The benefits that the legal system invests in corporations are a key element for the growth of businesses. At B&amp;amp;F Advocats we are prepared to protect your business interests in the area of Corporate Law, offering detailed guidance and advice on the various legal aspects of your day-to-day and long-term business activities.
We also help individuals decide whether establishing themselves as a corporation is a good choice on the long term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Nostre Despatx</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/temp/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/temp/about/</guid>
      <description>La nostra història B&amp;amp;F Advocats neix com a resultat d&amp;rsquo;una aliança conjunta de dos socis, Jose Luis Bou i Jose Antonio Feo, que van fer la transició des del sector privat, aportant cadascú diverses experiències.
El bufet es va fundar el setembre de l&amp;rsquo;any 2000 com una empresa arrelada en l&amp;rsquo;excel·lència legal i la ferma defensa dels valors de confiança i proximitat, amb l&amp;rsquo;objectiu de navegar pel complex panorama legal amb habilitat, i oferir sol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Law</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicework/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicework/work/</guid>
      <description>At B&amp;amp;F Advocats we advise clients on any and all matters of Employment Law, including both perspectives of the employment relationship, as a employer or as a worker. As with all of our practice areas, we will ensure your matters are handled discretely and confidentially.
Our experience in Employment Law Our employment law services cover a wide range of matters. Each of these unique areas of employment law is filled with very detailed and complex intricacies, and our experience and skill will help to succesfully navigate them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jose Antonio Feo</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/partners/feo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/partners/feo/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jose Luis Bou</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/partners/bou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/partners/bou/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Law</title>
      <link>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicetax/tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>bfirm.netlify.app/ca/practicetax/tax/</guid>
      <description>Tax Law is a vast area that concerns both individuals and companies. We offer individuals a guided advisement on tax duties and we perform the obligations before the Administration.
Our firm is fully prepared to deal with complex tax obligations, real-time reporting requirements, and increasing expectations of tax transparency.
Our experience in Tax Law Tax advisement is a matter of confidence. Our team has a proven experience with the comprehensive array of tax obligations arising from business activity or day-to-day individuals life, including:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
